Provided by Synchronized
The boy never knew his parents.
But was lucky enough
to be raised by his grandparents.
They were the best of friends
and worked in the lighthouse
of River's End.
But it was no ordinary lighthouse.
Every night,
Grandad turned on the light
to ward off a darkness
from another world.
The Huntsman.
Legend said if ever
the lighthouse light went out,
the Huntsman would enter the river
looking for Spirit Deer
adorned with magical antlers.
Their antlers made the water flow
and let life grow.
And if the Huntsman
took the magical antlers,
the rivers would dry up.
But,
for now, the lighthouse shines,
water flows,
and we all celebrate our river
with dance.
Oh.
Are you okay?
Good luck.
The around-the-world
hook-a-roo for the win!
Oh, Liam!
- Good shot.
- Thanks, Keegan.
- Stop!
- Uh, oh.
Leg it, lads.
Boys! You hit the cat!
Oh, I'm not very good at DJing.
You're gonna be a legend after this party.
Thanks, Margo.
Can I get a high five?
Oh, slightly missed it there.
Yeah, okay.
Don't screw up.
Joking!
But sort of in that way
that I'm not joking, you know?
Okay, have a good day!
Well, well, well,
look who it is.
I came as fast as I could.
Heavy traffic, woman.
Traffic?
Cheeky.
Just like your grandad.
The old fart will never admit it,
but he could use a little more help!
He's not as young as he used to be.
Hey!
I heard that.
He can hear when he wants to.
Which bit did you hear?
The old fart or the help?
I'll show you an old fart!
For your information,
I've aged like a fine leather wallet.
Now, if I could only find it,
I'd be a richer man too.
He's as mad as a box of frogs.
But he's hot.
Gross.
See you both
back at the cottage for supper.
Love you, me boyos.
Hoo-hoo!
Hey, Grandad.
Hey there, Mr. Hotshot DJ.
What other records did you get
for the St. Paddy's Day party?
Ready for a sneak preview?
My dancing slippers can hardly wait.
Here we go now.
Oh yeah!
Oh, yes. This brings me back.
Ooh.
My back.
Oof, I'll feel that one in the morning.
Ah, now. Ah.
Oh, cool.
We can use that for the Huntsman
in our paper theater.
Oh, now, that's pretty fat.
It's all brawn.
He needs to carry those antlers.
The Huntsman must never get
to those deer, Keegan.
Their dance keeps the rivers flowing.
Think about it.
Without the rivers,
no more life.
No more dance.
This is the one you must stop.
Luckily, it's just a legend.
Huh?
He's very real.
He's darkness,
and our magic light
is the only thing that can stop him.
Our light stops him?
I thought we just keep ships
from crashing into the rocks.
That's just an added bonus.
Now then, what do you say
we light this house up, hey, bucko?
Let's do it.
Race you up the stairs!
Right. Up the stairs we go.
Here we go.
There you go.
Are you okay?
Just wrecked from all that dancing is all.
And drumroll, please.
The tradition of warding off darkness
for another night.
- Easy, Grandad.
- I'm fine. Stop that now.
I'll just take a quick break.
You know, I was thinking,
why don't we automate this place?
It'd save so much time.
Where's the sport in that?
You don't automate your music, do you?
You prefer the spirit
in the vintage vinyl.
Same here.
We're more alike than you know.
You always say that, Grandad.
Now, relax.
I can clean up on my own.
Hey, Grandad, are you all right?
Grandad?
Grandad.
♪ Where the river foams ♪
♪ And surges to the sea ♪
♪ Silver figures rise ♪
♪ To find me ♪
♪ Wise and as daring ♪
♪ Following the heart's cry ♪
♪ I am that deep pool ♪
♪ I am that dark… ♪
I never got to say goodbye.
Do not mourn the man.
Celebrate the life.
Celebrate him with dance.
He would have loved this.
It was our favorite dance.
Your grandad is a tough act to follow.
Fastest feet I ever saw.
He was a legendary dancer.
He was unmatched on the hurling field.
He kept our seas and town safe.
You will too.
We're all counting on you
to carry on his traditions.
What do you say
we light this house up, hey, bucko?
No. The Huntsman
is just another one of your stories.
Stupid lighthouse!
Stupid traditions!
Stupid everything!
Get back here, you!
Pick it up!
Come on, boys!
Hey, Keegan.
Hey, Liam.
Big hurling game this weekend.
You in, little man?
Maybe another time.
Thanks anyway.
Okay. No problem, Keegan.
Hang in there, pal.
Hey, Keeg.
Hi, Moya.
Meet you at the waterfall
at high noon.
High noon?
Big things always happen at high noon.
It'll be worth it, I promise.
Oh my bananas!
- I...
- What?
- Wait, let me take my headphones off.
- I don't want to be the DJ!
There's no need to shout.
I don't want to be the DJ tonight.
Oh, no.
Oh, aren't you gonna give the people
what they want?
They all want you to DJ.
They be like, "Keegan!" "Keegan!"
"Keegan!"
- It's all different now.
- Oh.
Yeah. Come here.
It's okay, I… I understand.
You do?
Yeah, 'course I do.
Listen, I'll try to find
someone else to fill in.
You should just go and… take a walk.
Go out and get some fresh country air
into your lungs.
Walk?
To where?
I don't know.
Wherever the river leads you.
That was my Gandalf impression.
What's so funny?
I was just remembering this time
I was having a really rotten day,
and your grandad took me
to get some sweets and he…
Eugh. And he did this.
And that…
Oh, it's too funny.
Oh!
Oh, actually that…
That one is actually stuck up my…
Oh!
- Suppose you don't wanna eat that now?
- Ew!
No. Me neither. Hmm.
Hey! Did you know
sweets solve all problems?
It's true. It's scientifically proven.
Unless you're a dentist,
and then they are very much against that
as a problem-solving technique.
Well, whaddaya say
we drop by Sammie's Sugar Shack?
Yeah!
Huh?
Huh? Hey!
Oh!
Oh.
Eugh.
Oh!
Hey, give me those back.
Whoa!
Ha!
Oh!
Whoa!
Where are the brakes on this thing?
Oh!
Oh.
Hey, Keegan.
Whatcha doing?
Having a bad day.
Well, just keep hanging in there.
Very funny.
Help me up.
Oh!
Thanks.
What's that?
She's my new friend.
Why is she purple?
It's hair dye. I love purple.
So,
what are you doing out here?
It's noon.
We're right on schedule.
But I didn't...
Get ready for your mind
to be blown.
Sounds painful.
- Riddle time.
- What?
What always runs but never walks,
often murmurs, but never talks…
I can't balance and solve riddles
at the same time.
…has a bed but never sleeps,
has a mouth but never eats?
Oh my God, Keegan.
Ha-hoo.
Oh! Oh no.
Agh! I hate sheep!
Help!
Good luck!
Good luck?
You'll be fine. It's a fun ride.
¡Qué épico!
¡Allá vamos!
Woo!
Oh.
That was amazing!
The swoosh, swash, sweee
of all the rapids!
I love that part.
¡Qué divertido!
How are we gonna get back?
Back? We just got here.
Just got where?
What's going on?
Come on.
Don't be a Wussamus Maximus.
I am not a Wussamus Maximus.
Wait. What's a Wussamus Maximus?
Now what?
Whoa.
Oh!
There's no signal here.
Wouldn't help anyway.
The headphones were eaten,
the glass is cracked,
and now it's waterlogged.
Maybe we can dry it out.
Doubt it but nothing to lose.
How did you walk on water?
I didn't walk.
I danced.
Way harder.
So… confession time.
What?
I came here when my grandma died.
You did?
Where are we?
Some place magical.
Yeah, right.
I saw her.
She was here.
Impossible.
No, I told you.
Magical.
What happened when you saw her?
We danced.
Danced?
Flamenco. It was our thing.
I've never seen you dance flamenco.
We danced it all the time
when we lived in Spain.
But I haven't in a while.
Guess I've been trying to fit in
with the Irish-dancing thing.
Trying to fit in? You?
You're pretty good.
How come I've never seen you Irish dance?
I don't know.
How come I've never seen you flamenco?
How come you're not the DJ
at the party tonight?
I didn't want to celebrate.
I wanted to celebrate with you, Grandad.
Eugh!
Looks like Bette likes you.
And that's her husband, Rib.
Eugh.
Hello.
They apologize for stealing your sweets,
but it was to feed their 50 children, so…
- What?
- Well, 49 because they lost one, Adam.
They're wondering if we've seen him.
I haven't.
Sorry, guys.
Would you like nuts or berries
for breakfast?
I've been up for hours.
So,
you speak frog?
No, but Penny and Benny do.
Hey, little man.
Ta-da!
Hello, I'm Penny.
Name's Benny.
Shake my hand. It's cordiality.
You must be Keegan.
Heard a lot about you.
What's wrong with you?
I'm trying to scream,
but nothing is coming out!
Like in a nightmare.
He probably thinks you're gonna eat him.
Eat me?
Kid, kid, relax.
You're all skin and bones.
Plus, we already ate breakfast.
Some of us twice.
Hey, you.
You always do… Give me those back.
Oh.
I… I think I'm stuck.
.
I'm stuck.
What in the world are you doing?
I saw a girl do it in a film once.
Thought it was worth a try.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
You're awake.
Ow.
Huh?
Mm. They're coming!
Who?
- The other Megaloceros Giganteus.
- What?
- Wait, you've heard of us, right?
- Only in history class.
Megaloceros Giganteus.
Oh my...
Wow!
- Whoa!
- Woo-hoo!
Wow!
Whoa!
Yeah!
Bravo!
Welcome back, Moya.
- Thank you, Patrick.
- And you are?
He's my best friend, Keegan.
His grandad died, and he needs your help.
I am Patrick of the Megaloceros Giganteus.
Oh, yes.
That was not supposed to happen.
Get off me, Penny.
Penny, what happened?
What happened?
She's a wrecking ball with fur.
Mm-hmm!
Irish dancing is harder than it looks.
She's trying to fit in.
Like you.
As if I'm trying to fit in.
Then teach her your grandma's flamenco.
No.
Is that a chicken I smell?
Or just a big fat Wussamus Maximus?
It's hard to tell.
They smell so similar.
You know what, Penny?
Maybe you're more fire, less water.
Say what?
Maybe you're less Riverdance…
…and more flamenco.
Ooh…
Flamenco? Penny?
No way!
- I'll teach you, Penny.
- You will?
Oh my gosh. I love you!
Woo! BFFs!
Yas, girl! I am going to bring the heat,
like so much fire.
Excellent idea, Moya.
It was actually my idea.
I'm actually surprised
he's allowing the flamenco.
He's all Riverdance all the time.
Invented it.
Makes us dance every morning
to keep the rivers flowing
and life growing.
It's exhausting.
Penny and I usually hide.
Hmm.
I'm sorry about your grandad, Keegan.
It's okay.
No, it's not.
- Tell me about him.
- You have a year?
Maybe just the highlights.
Well, he was an amazing dancer,
a star hurler,
and an awesome lighthouse keeper.
Whoa.
Those are some big shoes to fill.
They were frog slippers.
And you haven't
the froggiest idea how to fill them?
- Boo!
- Oh.
- Terrible!
- Dad-joke alert.
I'm sorry, bad joke.
We all feel
a little lost sometimes, Keegan.
The good news is
you've come to the right place.
Follow me. I think I can help.
- Where are we going?
- We're going crazy!
Wanna come?
We follow the river, Keegan.
Rivers connect everything and everyone.
And the energy we create
while celebrating them,
we return to them.
Their waters not only create life.
They are life.
His antlers are sick!
Are you implying mine aren't?
No, no, no, no.
I… I didn't say anything about yours.
They're travel-size, buddy.
Let's leave it at that.
Okay.
If the teachers were wrong,
and you didn't go extinct,
then how old are you guys?
Patrick is the oldest,
which makes him about…
400,000 years old.
Whoa. How old are you?
I mean, honestly, I don't even know, man.
I lost count around 200,000.
Ever try to count that high, yeah?
I was counting and counting and counting,
and then I was like, "Screw it!"
Don't need it.
- You're all right, Benny.
- No foolin'?
No foolin'.
Oh, I am serving hoof,
serving hoof, serving face.
So, Moya, how good do I look right now?
Well, you seem very limber
and have a unique style,
so definitely steps
in the right direction.
Yes!
The right direction!
Better than the wrong direction!
Now, try not to think.
Don't worry. I'm not.
Good because flamenco
comes from the heart.
Whoa! Deep.
Twirly-dwirly.
Hmm?
Does he say anything else, this guy?
- He's probably gassy.
- What?
I saw him chowing on some swamp grass
back there like it was going out of style.
Ever been around a butt that big
when it lets one go? Poo!
It's like a bomb inside a hurricane.
You know, I'm only, like,
five feet in front of you,
and I can hear everything you're saying.
Oh, he farted out a baby swamp rock.
Ew!
Whoa. That's nasty.
That was not me.
My bad.
Never mind.
It's just a hurling ball
gone out of bounds.
I thought
you were a baby swamp rock.
No way.
You guys play hurling?
We have to stay in shape
for dancing somehow, don't we?
Only three minutes left
and the game is tied!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Good block!
- Let's go. Let's go. Hup, hup, let's go.
- I got it!
- Oh, it looks so painful.
- That's gotta hurt.
Gonna be a while until they get unstuck.
- Who wants to fill in for them?
- Not it!
Moya's still teaching me flamenco,
so we're out.
- Keegan and Benny, you're the lucky ones.
- No, I really don't want to.
This is the exact opposite of lucky!
Benny, you're goalie.
Keegan, you're corner forward.
Patrick, I don't want to play.
Your grandad was a star hurler, right?
- Taught me everything.
- Well, then make him proud.
You get on that field,
and you do what he taught you.
Birds! Hurley stick, helmet.
Crack hardy.
Not me!
Him!
Awesome.
Guys, color up.
Benny, smear it on your antlers.
Don't drink it.
I know, but come on!
They're raspberries,
and they're so delicious.
Great. We lose our two best players
and get stuck with these guys.
Well, there goes the playoffs.
Victory is ours!
Team sports. Yay.
Slap it!
Great pass!
Yeah, buddy!
Let's go!
Come on. Yeah!
Too easy.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Up! Up!
Good block!
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
It's gonna hurt! It's gonna hurt!
Yeah!
Awesome job, Benny!
Booyah!
That's what tiny antlers can do for you!
Watch it, kid.
Come on, Keegan, me boyo.
Get up and play.
Play like your grandad is watching.
No way!
Oh, come on!
This one's for you, Grandad.
You did it, kid!
- Yeah!
- Awesome!
Keegan! Keegan! Woo!
- Amazing.
- Red team wins!
Don't be a brute, Brutus.
Go get that ball back.
Don't worry.
I'll get it.
Attention, ladies and gentledeer.
Get ready to be razzle-dazzled.
Pull the alarm because Penny's on fire!
Heel, toe, repose and…
serve to the left, serve to the right,
serving face all night long.
Here we go and…
Oh!
Serving! Face!
Woah!
Aww.
No, I'm fine.
You know, in retrospect, I shouldn't have
started on the top of a hill.
So, any luck finding Adam?
Well, I mean, he can't be far.
He doesn't have legs.
You'll find him. Cheer up.
Tiny tadpole kisses!
They tickle!
Whoa.
What is this place?
A bridge
between light and dark.
You're the Huntsman.
I take many forms, but…
guilty as charged.
I'll scream,
and the others will come for me.
You're the one who left the light off.
Where I'm from, that's an invitation.
No! I...
As a token of gratitude,
I have a proposition for you.
Come to my world,
and you can have everything
back the way it was.
My grandad said to never trust you.
Suit yourself.
Oh, and Keegan,
I wouldn't tell anyone you saw me
because then they'd know what you did.
Inviting me in.
Wouldn't want them
to get the wrong idea, right?
See you round.
Keegan!
- Keegan!
Hey, little man.
Where'd you go?
We've been looking all over for you.
You missed Penny's dance.
Classic Penny disaster-piece theater.
So funny!
Benny! Manners!
Benny, be nice.
She almost had it.
She'll honor us with it one day.
.
You look like you've seen a ghost.
The thing about that is…
Just a little afraid of the dark is all.
Ah, yes.
That's because this is a place
where one faces one's darkest fears.
- I'm not afraid of anything.
- You're afraid of everything, Benny.
No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
Oh yeah? Caterpillars!
Where? Where?
Are they on me?
Are they in my mouth?
Keegan, this is a lighthouse
from times past.
If you faced your fear here,
you can banish darkness.
You are a keeper of light,
passed from one ancestor to the next,
all the way to you.
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Where are we going?
All the way to the sea.
- No!
Is that bad?
- Yes!
Why?
- Because it's so much walking!
Don't worry, I know a shortcut.
The great gate.
This is the gate through which spirits
from the past, present, and future pass.
Finn MacCool,
Cú Chulainn and the Children of Lir
have all come through here too.
Do you think my grandad came through here?
Ah, you'll have to ask the gatekeeper.
Um…
Did an old guy come through here?
You know, big nose, frog slippers?
And big ears, like yours?
He danced through here, boy.
He said you were
keeping his traditions alive.
- Well, uh…
- Huh?
Keegan, come here.
This is where
I saw my grandma, Keegan.
I don't see anything.
Close your eyes.
How can I see anything if I close my...
Grandad!
Do you know why I dance?
There's a rhythm to the river
as it hits the sea.
It means life is still going.
You should always celebrate life.
I want to go back!
No!
Keegan, son, where are you?
Down here, Grandad!
The Huntsman.
The Huntsman is coming.
You need to light the lighthouse!
No!
♪ Hear my cry ♪
♪ In my hungering search for you ♪
What have I done?
Keegan!
Moya!
I got you!
I forgot how to gallop!
It's been so long since I've exercised!
Just real quick, how do you gallop?
Keep galloping now.
Yeah!
Cramp! Cramp!
Help!
Benny!
Look at his travel-size antlers!
I know, right?
Oh, that's not so bad.
Huh?
Oh no! No!
Bad Huntsman! Bad Huntsman!
Don't worry.
You're just bait.
He's the one I want.
Now, your antlers
are the ultimate prize.
Run, Benny!
It's a trap.
He looks stupid, but he's clever!
Get out of here, Keegan.
Patrick!
Keegan, look out!
Let go of me!
The kid
for the antlers.
Give me your antlers,
and we can all go home.
Why?
With the power to stop rivers,
I can spread darkness everywhere.
Patrick, don't do it.
No, Patrick!
Get your hands off me!
Quiet, boy!
You knew this would happen.
The river.
The river's gone!
Oh.
Huh?
Stop!
You can't stop me!
You should thank me!
No river,
no need to protect it with a light,
no need to celebrate it with a dance.
You're free!
Keegan, the Hunter
must not leave our world
with Patrick's antlers.
You must return the antlers to the water.
The water will renew his spirit.
Can you help me turn his raft around?
Come on! One more time!
No!
♪ How can the small flowers grow ♪
♪ If the wild winds blow ♪
♪ And the cold snow is all around ♪
♪ Where will the frail birds fly ♪
♪ If their homes on high ♪
♪ Have been torn down ♪
♪ To the ground ♪
♪ Lift the Wings ♪
♪ That carry me away from here ♪
♪ And fill the sail ♪
♪ That breaks the line to home ♪
♪ And when I'm miles and miles ♪
♪ Apart from you ♪
♪ I'm beside you when I think of you ♪
Buachaill.
Attaboy.
Watch your foot.
♪ How can a tree stand tall ♪
That was awesome!
♪ …If a rain won't fall ♪
You faced darkness and won.
You are truly a keeper of light.
♪ And how can the heart survive ♪
♪ Can it stay alive ♪
♪ If its love's denied for long ♪
♪ Lift the Wings ♪
♪ That carry me away from here ♪
♪ And fill the sail ♪
♪ That breaks the line to home ♪
♪ And when I'm miles and miles ♪
♪ Apart from you ♪
Thank goodness he's back.
Have you seen Rib and Bette?
♪ A Stóirín ♪
♪ And I'm with you
When I dream of you ♪
♪ A Stóirín ♪
♪ And a song will bring you near to me ♪
♪ A Grá ♪
Yes, tadpoles, jet it!
Oh! Baby frogs now!
Confrogulations!
Oh!
Hey, Moya, look who figured you out.
I liked when you thought
I could walk on water.
I still do.
Wait. How are the rivers still flowing
without Patrick's antlers?
I think you'll be pleasantly surprised.
O-M-G!
Did he just go through puberty?
Goodbye, travel-size antlers.
Hello, king-size antlers!
It couldn't have happened
to a better deer, Benny.
Benny? Why does he get to be king?
Sometimes those you think
are the least able
prove to be the most capable.
I didn't ask for this job.
But I have to admit,
these antlers are pretty sweet.
Looking good.
Sorry to leave,
but I have to get back home
and turn on the lighthouse.
That's a good idea.
The Huntsman will never stop hunting,
and now you have to protect this guy.
What? He's coming for me next?
Thank you so much
for helping me find my fire.
It's all you, Penny.
Please turn that light on.
I still have no idea how to gallop!
And I'm a really slow learner!
I think I'm gonna be sick.
You're all right, Benny.
I got this.
Bye!
- Bye!
- Good luck, Keegan!
- See you later, alligator.
Agh. Whoa!
I was hoping you could say goodbye
to your grandad.
It's okay.
Thank you for trying.
The river.
It's the river!
What?
Your riddle.
"What always runs but never walks,
often murmurs, never talks,
has a bed but never sleeps,
has a mouth but never eats?"
The river!
I hope she comes back.
Me too.
I've been dreaming
of lamb chops for dinner.
What?
Oh, sheep!
- Run!
- Huh?
Ooh!
So, meet you
at the St. Patrick's Day party?
Uh, hate to break it to you,
but that was yesterday.
No, it wasn't.
We've only been gone a couple of hours.
How is that possible?
I told you it was magical.
Happy St. Patrick's Day.
Happy St. Paddy's Day.
So, there's still time
for you to dance the flamenco tonight?
I've committed to the Riverdance.
Oh, trying to fit in.
Wussamus Maximus.
My favorite DJ quit.
♪ Wussamus Maximus ♪
Glad I caught you.
Hi. Oh, sorry.
You just caught me fiddling around.
What are you looking at me
like that for? Look.
It's a fiddle.
Do you still need a DJ tonight?
Oh, sorry, bud, but Larson volunteered.
Larson stinks!
I don't stink.
And I didn't volunteer.
I was winking, Larson,
to get Keegan super jealous
and teach him an invaluable life lesson,
one for which he will never forget
across the rivers of time.
So I'm still the DJ?
Only if you buy this fiddle.
- Um…
- I'm kidding!
Yes, you're still the DJ.
Awesome. Thanks, Margo.
But, Larson, you are going
to have to buy this fiddle.
- I hate the fiddle!
- Nobody likes the fiddle.
That's why I can't sell it, but just
like broccoli and alternative jazz,
you learn to put up with it.
Hey, guys.
- Hey, Keegan.
- Hey.
If you're still looking
for another hurler,
I'm your guy.
Of course.
- Yes!
A green river for good luck.
Enjoy the brew, fishies!
Hey.
Has that deer always been there?
That ain't no deer.
That there is the Megaloceros Giganteus.
- They're legends.
- Do you think they invented Riverdance?
Shh!
That's a secret.
Hi, honey.
What have you been up to today?
Nothing.
They look like antlers.
He loved the deer.
Always said it was his spirit animal.
What do you think?
Ribbit!
Dancing slippers are totally in.
You know, I'm still not sure
if I want to go to the party tonight.
First one without my dancing partner.
I know how you feel.
Put it on.
It's too big.
What are you talking about, "too big"?
It fits you perfectly.
You're the spitting image of him, Keegan.
Right down to his big ears.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Love you, my boyo.
The tradition of warding off
darkness for another night.
Grandad.
I'm proud of you, me bucko.
I can't stay.
I know.
Will you be all right?
Oh, I'll be better than all right.
I'll be dancing!
Goodbye, Grandad.
Let's dance!
So proud of you, Moya.
Great job!
Hoop it! Woo!
Stop! Fellas!
But the fish love the green brew.
- Leg it, lads!
- Come on, it's St. Patrick's Day.
Keegan! Keegan! Keegan!
Woo!
Happy St. Patrick's Day!
Hey, when are you gonna dance?
What makes you think I'm not?
♪ I can see the light
It's falling in your eyes ♪
♪ We will rise above
The darkness of the night ♪
♪ So let's all stand as one
Together we can fight ♪
♪ I can see the lighthouse ♪
♪ I can see the light ♪
♪ Soon who will realize
The fire shines so bright? ♪
♪ It lives inside of you
Can feel the beat in time ♪
♪ So darling, take my hand
Let's burn the night sky ♪
♪ 'Cause I can see the lighthouse ♪
♪ I can see the light ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Into the night sky ♪
♪ Together we'll fly ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Into the night sky ♪
♪ Together we'll fly ♪
♪ Let me up
Let me up ♪
♪ Let the star keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ The dark makes me shine brighter ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ Hear the people sing
And watch the rivers run ♪
♪ Follow your heart and dreams
The journey's just begun ♪
♪ The dark will call your name
And storms will hide the song ♪
♪ I can see the lighthouse ♪
♪ I can see the light ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Into the night sky ♪
♪ Together we'll fly ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Into the night sky ♪
♪ Together we'll fly ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ The dark makes me shine brighter ♪
♪ Let me up
Let me up ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ You will find your way ♪
♪ Never lose your faith ♪
♪ Keep believing ♪
♪ Can you feel it? ♪
♪ You will find your way ♪
♪ Never lose your faith ♪
♪ Keep believing ♪
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ The dark makes me shines brighter ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
♪ The dark makes me shine brighter ♪
♪ Like a star,
I keep on rising ♪
♪ Let me up ♪
All right, there's gonna be
some changes around here.
Hurling is banned,
at least for me.
And so is early-morning dancing.
And you know something?
I get to eat
as many raspberries as I want.
Y'all cool with that?
Doesn't matter 'cause I'm in charge now.
King Benny!
- What?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Uh, can somebody help me up?
These new antlers are really heavy.
What a jerk.
- Oh, what a disappointment.
- Let's get outta here.
I'm… I'm sorry. I'll do better.
It's my first day at this,
and it kind of went to my head.
Literally.
Hmm, classic Benny disaster-piece theater.
Well, bye.
Megaloceros Giganteuses?
Friends-euses?
Where my friends-euses at, huh?
Wanna help?
Wanna help your old pal Benny up?
Anybody wanna help Benny?
Benny? Wanna help Benny,
your old buddy Benny?
Anybody, buddy, Benny, help Benny?
.
Poo.
What if I have to poo? What do I do?
Hey, everybody.
This next one is for Megaloceros
and mega grandparents everywhere!
♪ Hear my cry ♪
♪ In my hungering search for you ♪
♪ Taste my breath on the wind ♪
♪ See the sky ♪
♪ As it mirrors my colors ♪
♪ Hints and whispers begin ♪
♪ I am living to nourish you ♪
♪ Cherish you ♪
♪ I am pulsing the blood in your veins ♪
♪ Feel the magic and power ♪
♪ Of surrender to life ♪
♪ Uisce Beatha ♪
♪ Every finger is touching ♪
♪ Searching until your secrets come out ♪
♪ In the dance as it endlessly circles ♪
♪ I linger close to your mouth ♪
♪ I am living to nourish you ♪
♪ Cherish you ♪
♪ I am pulsing the blood in your veins ♪
♪ Feel the magic and power
Of surrender to life ♪
♪ Uisce Beatha ♪